gogoro.com 2016-05-09

# Gogoro - Introducing the world's first and only Smartscooter™

## Gogoro Privacy Policy

This Gogoro Privacy Policy was updated on January, 5 2015.

Your privacy is important to Gogoro. Gogoro Inc., its affiliates and/or subsidiaries (collectively, “Gogoro”, “we”, “us” or “our”) have developed this privacy policy (“Gogoro Privacy Policy”) to protect the information derived from your use of Gogoro’s web site (the “Site”) that Gogoro collects, stores, uses, and under certain conditions, discloses, shares, or transfers. Gogoro may collect, use, disclose, share, transfer or store your Personal Information and Non-Personal Information according to the provisions of Gogoro Privacy Policy. By visiting the Site, you accept the practices described in Gogoro Privacy Policy.

### Personal Information Gogoro May Collect and Use

Personal Information Gogoro may collect  
While visiting the Site, you may be asked to provide Gogoro with “Personal Information” for different purposes, and Gogoro will collect and may store such Personal Information. Personal information includes information that specifically identifies an individual, including but not limited to, name, mailing address, email address, telephone number, mobile number or employer.

For instance, by requesting Gogoro to notify you of updates to Gogoro’s products or updates to the Site, Gogoro may ask you to provide your personal email address. In addition, you may submit to Gogoro messages that include information that can facilitate communication with Gogoro including your name, personal telephone number, mobile number, or your employer.

For Personal Information received by Gogoro, it shall be deemed that you knowingly and specifically agreed to provide such Personal Information. In no event shall you provide any Personal Information of any third party without such third party’s prior consent. If you do not agree to provide your Personal Information, Gogoro may not be able to inform you of any updates including, but not limited to, updates to Gogoro products, Terms of Use or Gogoro Privacy Policy.

Personal Information Gogoro may use  
Gogoro may use your Personal Information by Gogoro itself, or through or together with its affiliates, subsidiaries or strategic partners by disclosure, share or transfer of your Personal Information to such affiliates, subsidiaries or strategic partners, for purposes below including: 

  * to provide the services, products, or information you request, and to process and complete such requests and any related transactions;
  * to send you confirmations, updates, alerts, and support and administrative messages and otherwise facilitate your use of, and our administration and operation of, the Site;
  * to keep you informed about various promotions, offers, events, products or services;
  * to send you notices, such as changes to the Site, the Terms of Use, Gogoro Privacy Policy or any other policy or guideline;
  * for internal purposes, such as research, auditing or data analysis; or
  * to comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.

### Non-Personal Information Gogoro May Collect and Use

Non-Personal Information Gogoro may collect  
Once you visit the Site or act on a Gogoro email, Gogoro or Gogoro’s strategic partners may use some technologies to collect “Non Personal Information” about your usage of or activity on the Site that cannot, on its own, identify or allow direct association with a specific individual. Non-Personal Information may include, without limitation, information collected by or through web beacons or cookies.

For instance, web beacons are electronic images that we use on the Site or in Gogoro email that Gogoro sends to you, for the purpose of understanding your usage when you open or take any action via the email.

Non-Personal Information Gogoro may use  
Gogoro Privacy Policy does not limit our use or disclosure of any Non-Personal Information in any way, and we reserve the right to use and disclose Non-Personal Information to our affiliates, subsidiaries or its strategic partners at our discretion. For instance, such Non-Personal Information may be used to better understand your behavior, to realize which parts of the Site that visitors have visited, and to facilitate and measure the effectiveness of advertisements and web searches. 

### Protecting Your Personal Information

Gogoro will take reasonable and appropriate measures to prevent your Personal Information provided by you from unauthorized or unlawful access, use, processing, or alteration, and from any breaches or loss of such Personal Information. Such measures may be implemented through use of a third party service. You are solely responsible for any Personal Information you choose to share or submit in public areas of the Site, such as a forum or a message board.

Despite Gogoro taking reasonable steps to use and improve various safeguards, you acknowledge and agree that no system or technology is completely secure and safe. If you become aware of any vulnerability of the Site, please email [contact@gogoro.com](mailto:contact@gogoro.com) or visit the Site to report such vulnerability.

### Children

Gogoro is not intended for children under thirteen (13) years of age. Gogoro, its affiliates, subsidiaries or its strategic partners do not knowingly or intentionally collect, disclose, share, transfer any Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13) and you should not, under any circumstance or for any reason, provide your Personal Information if you are under the age of thirteen (13). If Gogoro becomes aware of any collection of any Personal Information of a child under the age of thirteen (13), Gogoro will take steps to delete such Personal Information.

### Changes to Gogoro Privacy Policy

Gogoro may change the provisions of Gogoro Privacy Policy at any time. If we change or update Gogoro Privacy Policy, we will indicate that changes have been made by updating the effective date of Gogoro Privacy Policy. Gogoro encourages you to review Gogoro Privacy Policy from time to time to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide may be used.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments about Gogoro Privacy Policy, please send an email to [contact@gogoro.com](mailto:contact@gogoro.com).

Copyright © 2014-2016 Gogoro Inc. All rights reserved.
